One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The New World
Yeni Dünya
Mink Guardians
Mink Muhafızları
Master Nekomamushi is quite a skilled navigator!
Usta Nekomamushi'nin denizcilik yetenekleri müthiş!
I'd expect no less from a man who sailed with the King of the Pirates!
Korsanlar Kralı ile denize açılmış bir adama da ancak bu yakışır!
Now, how much longer do we have to wait at these ruins?
Bu harabede ne kadar bekleyeceğiz?
Until Master Nekomamushi brings Marco here!
Usta Nekomamushi, Marco ile dönene kadar!
I wonder if he'll show...
Gelecek mi acaba?
If Marco accompanies us to Wano, he'll make for a strong ally.
Marco'nun bizimle Wano'ya gelmesi güçlü bir müttefikimiz olacak demek!
Marco is the former First Division commander of the infamous Whitebeard Pirates!
Marco eski Beyazsakal Korsanları'nın 1. Tümen Komutanı!
He's known as Marco the Phoenix!
Anka Marco diyorlar ona!
What a surprise to find out that he's Master's friend.
Ustanın arkadaşı olduğunu duyunca şaşırdım.
Alright!
Pekâlâ!
I'm gonna get a look at that man for myself.
Ben de onu görmeye gideceğim.
Whoa! Wait, wait, wait!
Hey! Bekle, bekle, bekle!
Master told you to wait here because you-gara have a scary face!
Usta, o korkunç-gara suratın yüzünden burada beklemeni istedi!
Is he the kind of guy who'd get scared by my face?!
Marco gerçekten yüzümden korkacak birisi mi?
That's not the point.
Bak!
He said there's a peaceful village on the other side of the cave behind that waterfall...
Şelalenin arkasındaki mağaranın diğer tarafında huzurlu bir köy varmış.
A group of warriors like us would terrify the locals.
Bizim gibi savaşçılar, onları korkutur.
True.
Haklısın.
But Master Nekomamushi's face is scarier than mine!
Gel gör ki Usta'nın yüzü benimkinden daha korkunç!
Yes, when he gets mad.
Hele bir de kızdığında.
But he's cute when he smiles.
Gülerken de sevimli oluyor!
For sure!
Aynen!
Onward to Wano
Wano'ya Doğru
There!
İşte!
Hey, wait!
Hey, bekle!
Okay.
Bitti.
His treatment is complete.
Tedavi işi tamamdır.
He can go now.
Hareket edebilir.
He said you can go now.
Hareket edebilirmişsin!
Tama, can you stand?
Tama, kalkabilir misin?
Easy does it.
Yavaş ol.
My Flames of Restoration can only help others so much.
İyileştiren Alevler'imin başkaları üzerindeki etkisi sınırlı.
Marco Former 1st Division Commander (Ship's Doctor) Whitebeard Pirates
Marco Eski Beyazsakal Korsanları Üyesi 1. Tümen Komutanı (Doktor)
With this treatment, he should heal faster.
Bu tedaviyle daha hızlı iyileşecektir.
He'll be jumping around by tomorrow.
Yarın hoplayıp zıplayabileceksin.
Wow! Marco is magic!
Vay! Marco'nun büyüsü!
Isn't it great, Tama?!
Harika değil mi, Tama?!
Wow! That was amazing!
Vay! Harika!
You're okay now, Tama!
İyileştin, Tama!
I said, "By tomorrow"! No jumping yet!
Yarın dedim! Zıplamayı kes!
Thanks, Marco!
Teşekkürler, Marco!
You're the best!
Sen bir tanesin!
– Marco...
– Marco... – Marco-san...
My poor, stiff shoulders...
Omzum tutuldu...
Nekomamushi Mink Guardians
Nekomamushi Mink Muhafızı
Marco, at the mountain...
Marco, dağda...
Marco, my crops...
Marco, tarlamdaki sebzeler...
Marco, my back hurts again!
Marco, sırt ağrılarım geri döndü!
– Marco, my knees... – Marco, can you help me study?
- Marco-chan, dizlerim... - Marco, çalışmama yardım eder misin?
Marco, my little brother is mean to me!
Marco, kardeşim bana kötü davranıyor!
All right. I'll hear you out one by one.
Tamam, teker teker konuşun.
This is the village Pops built...
Bu köyü Babalık inşa etti.
Old man Whitebeard?
İhtiyar Beyazsakal mı?
What do you mean?
Ne demek istiyorsun?
Due to the extreme poverty in this area...
Çok fakir olduklarından...
folks here can't afford the heavenly tribute to join the World Government...
kutsal vergiyi ödeyemiyorlar. Böyle olunca Hükûmet'e bağlı olamıyorlar.
That's how it goes with nonmember nations.
Hükûmet'e bağlı olmayan ülkelerin hâli bu.
Pirates and human traffickers do as they please, turning those islands lawless.
Korsanlar ve insan tacirleri istediklerini yapıp o adaları kanunsuz hâle getiriyorlar.
The countries go to ruins and many of their children become orphans...
Ülkeler yıkılıyor ve çocuklar öksüz kalıyor.
Pops was one of those children.
Babalık da o yetimlerden birisiydi.
And he set out to sea at an early age.
Genç yaşta denize açılmış.
Even after he became a pirate, he still cared about this island...
Korsan olduktan sonra bile bu adayla ilgilendi.
He kept his identity a secret while funneling his dirty money and resources here...
Kimliğini gizleyerek kara para ve...
for the rest of his life.
erzak aktardı.
Even back then, he didn't have a family, and all his friends were gone...
Bir ailesi yoktu ve eski arkadaşları göçüp gitmişti ama...
This was his home nonetheless.
burası onun memleketiydi.
In this corrupt world, there's no such thing as clean money!
Yozlaşmış dünyada temiz paradan söz edilemez!
Thank you...
Teşekkürler.
After the Summit War...
Zirve Savaşı'ndan sonra...
we at least tried to defend the things that Pops was protecting
en azından değer verdiği şeyleri korumak istedik.
so we kicked off the Payback War against Blackbeard as he invaded our territory.
Kara Sakal bölgemizi istila ettiğinde, "İntikam Savaşı" başladı.
But we were no match for Teach and the power he got from Pops.
Ancak Babalığın gücüne sahip olduğundan Teach ile baş edemedik.
He took everything from us...
Her şeyi aldı.
I wanted to beat the hell out of that ingrate...
O nankörün pestilini çıkarmak istemiştim.
Pops was...
Babalık...
He was pretty stingy, wasn't he?
çok cimriydi, ha?
He often wanted others' drinks...
Hep başkalarının içkilerini isterdi.
and never got any for us!
Asla bir şey ısmarlamazdı!
Since his entire share of our treasure went back to this village...
Neticede hazinedeki tüm payını buraya gönderirdi.
We all knew it!
Bunu bilmeyen yoktu.
I see...
Anlıyorum.
So, in essence, this village acts as his final memento.
Burası ihtiyardan kalma son yadigâr, ha?
Yeah...
Evet.
And...
Kızıl Saç da...
Red Hair buried him nearby...
mezarını yakın bir yere yaptı.
By the way...
Bu arada...
there's a Warlord named Weevil claiming he's Pops' biological son...
Babalığın oğlu olduğunu söyleyip onunla alakası olanlara saldıran...
who attacks people connected to Whitebeard.
Weevil adında bir Shichibukai var.
Oh, is that true?!
Doğru mu bu?
If we're talking about his love life, one can't be certain...
Babalığın kadınlarla olan mazisi hakkında bir yorum yapamam,
but I'd wager they're after his fortune.
ama sanırım miras peşindeler.
As if they'd take our word for it that it doesn't exist.
Miras falan yok desek inanmayacaklardır.
I figure that sooner or later he'll come after me and this place.
Er geç, benim ve buranın peşine düşecektir.
I see.
Anladım.
So you can't leave right meow.
Öyleyse buradan ayrılamazsın, miyav.
Weevil's mother Buckin used to be a pirate.
Weevil'ın annesi Buckin, eski bir korsan.
I know that thirty or forty years ago, she was on the same ship with Pops.
30 veya 40 yıl önce falan Babalık ile aynı gemideymiş.
Then, maybe he's also a memento that should be protected.
Belki de korunması gereken başka bir yadigârdır.
His behavior sure would suggest otherwise!
Davranışları aksini gösteriyor!
You're right!
Haklısın.
If you're going to see Straw Hat Luffy, I want you to pass on a message, Nekomamushi.
Hasır Şapka Luffy'yle buluşacaksan ona bir mesajım var, Nekomamushi.
Yeah, no problem.
Cankulağıyla dinliyorum.
You said you're headed to Wano?
Hedefiniz Wano mu dedin?
Yep.
Evet.
At Sea New World
Yeni Dünya Suları
Luffy! It says the Reverie has begun!
Luffy! Reverie başlamış!
Monarchs from all over the world are attending the conference at Mary Geoise!
Dünyanın dört bir yanından hükümdarlar, Mary Geoise'daki konferansa katılıyor!
All eyes are on the Ryugu Kingdom
Bu seferki konferansta ise tüm gözler...
since they're participating for the first time in two centuries!
iki asırdır ilk kez katıldıkları için Ryugu Krallığı'na çevrilmiş durumda!
King Neptune and his sons are there...!
Neptune-san ile oğullarının fotoğrafını çekmişler.
And it looks like Shirahoshi was applauded at the Red Port!
Red Port'ta Shirahoshi'ye alkış seli olmuş!
So she came up to the surface!
Karaya çıkmış demek!
Wimpyhoshi is getting stronger!
Bizim Pısırıkhoshi güçlenmiş!
Captain "Straw Hat" Luffy Straw Hat Pirates Bounty: ¬1.5 Billion
"Hasır Şapkalı" Luffy Hasır Şapka Korsanları Kaptanı Kelle Ödülü: ¬1.5 Milyar
It seems like your grandpa was their escort.
Anlaşılan deden onların refakatçisiymiş.
Oh...?
Ya...?
They took a big step toward their dream to relocate the Fishmen to the surface!
Balıkadamları yüzeye taşıma hayallerine doğru büyük bir adım atmışlar!
Vivi sweetie!
Vivi-chwan!
You became an even more beautiful princess!
Daha da güzel bir prenses olmuşsun!
And who could it be for?
Kimin gönlünü çalmak için?
Me?! Hey, is it for me?!
Benim mi? Hey, benim için mi?!
Move!
Çekil!
Vivi!
Vivi!
It's Vivi!
Bizim Vivi!
It's been forever since we last saw her!
Onu görmeyeli uzun zaman oldu!
She's become a graceful and regal princess!
Zarif ve krallara layık bir prenses olmuş.
Oh, so this is Vivi.
Oh, demek bu Vivi-san.
If we ever meet, I'd like to see her panties–
Onunla karşılaşınca külotunu görmek isterim–
Like she'd show you!
Gösterir mi hiç sana!
Oh, these are photos from the Unity Courtyard...
Bu fotoğraflar Sosyalleşme Alanı'nda çekilmiş.
Look at all the royals who attended with their bodyguards.
İştirak eden kraliyet ailelerine ve korumalarına baksanıza!
I-If Dressrosa is participating...
D-Dressrosa da katılıyorsa...
There she is! Viola my lovely!
İşte! Viola-chan!
It's Wapol!
Bu Wapol!
The acorn guy is there, too!
Palamut amca da yanında!
What? Wapol?!
Ne? Wapol mu?
Did he make a comeback?!
Geri mi döndü?!
Rebecca! Sai!
Rebecca! Sai!
We know so many of them!
Birçok tanıdık yüz var!
Of course.
E hâliyle.
Royals from all around the world gather at the Reverie to discuss issues!
Dünyanın dört bir yanından Reverie'ye gelip istişare ediyorlar!
Oh, maybe at the Reverie...
Oh, belki Reverie'de...
At the Reverie, the princesses that I know...
Reverie'de, tanıştığım prensesler...
are getting worked up talking about me!
hakkımda konuşmaktan yerinde duramıyorlardır!
Wouldn't that be nice?
Ne güzel olurdu, değil mi?
Hey, look at this, Chopper!
Hey, baksana Chopper!
Right here!
Şuraya!
What is it, Chobro?
Ne oldu, Choniki?
Doctorine!
Doktorin!
Oh, is she still alive?
Hadi ya, daha ölmemiş mi?
Hey!
Hey!
Doctorine...
Doktorin...
Hey! What are you doing, Chopper?!
Hey! Ne halt yiyorsun Chopper?
Don't cut it out!
Kesmesene!
What? Wait!
Ne? Dur biraz!
Give me back my princesses!
Prenseslerimi bana ver!
What are you doing?!
N'apıyorsunuz ya?
Hey! I haven't read the other side yet!
Hey! Henüz arka sayfayı okumamıştım!
It's full of holes!
Delik deşik etmişsiniz!
Oh? Is this an article about Kaido?
Ha? Kaido hakkında yazı mı var?
Big Mom... is what?! I can't even read it!
Big Mom... Ne yapıyormuş? Okunmuyor ki!
Sanji! Chopper! Give those back to me!
Sanji-kun! Chopper! Verin şunları!
– No!
– Olmaz!
I'm glad everyone's doing great!
Hepsini de iyi gördüğüme sevindim!
Once we sail around the world, let's visit them again!
Dünyayı dolaşmayı bitirince ziyaretlerine gidelim!
Yes! All in good order!
Evet! Durumları iyiymiş!
Anyway, Luffy, the transponder snail still won't connect?
Bu arada Luffy-san, aktarıcı salyangoz hâlâ çalışmıyor mu?
Oh, I forgot.
Sahi, aklımdan çıkmış.
Hey! This is Luffy!
Hey! Benim, Luffy!
Come in!
Cevap verin!
There's no response.
Cevap yok yav.
Whatever. Let's push on!
Önemli değil, devam edelim!
Wait, Luffy!
Bekle, Luffy!
What's wrong?
Ne oldu?
The wind...
Rüzgâr...
The chill on the wind... and I've never seen waves like these...
Soğuk rüzgârla daha önce hiç görmediğim biçimdeki dalgalar...
This can only spell trouble.
kesinlikle hayra alamet değil!
So this is the sea that surrounds Wano!
Wano çevresindeki deniz sahasına geldik demek!
The wind is getting stronger as we draw closer, and the waves are getting bigger!
Yaklaştıkça rüzgâr şiddeti gibi dalga boyları da artıyor!
It doesn't look like a normal wind-driven current.
Bu kabarma, rüzgârın sürüklediği sıradan bir akıntıya benzemiyor.
In addition to the unusual current...
Sıra dışı dalgaların yanı sıra...
Look! That's some nasty weather!
gökyüzündeki korkunç havaya baksana!
We'll want to avoid the storm...
Fırtınadan kaçınmak akıllıca olur.
Shall we wait it out?
Dinmesini bekleyelim mi?
Hey! What are you talking about, Brook?!
Hey! Ne diyorsun, Brook?
Let's go to Wano now!
Wano'ya hemen gidiyoruz!
Luffy, why would you put your crew in such obvious danger?
Luffy-san, niye hep mürettebatını bariz bir tehlikeye sokmak istiyorsun ki?
Y'know, Brook...
Şöyle ki Brook...
Huh?
Ha?
Kin'emon actually warned me about this...
Kin'emon bu konuda bizi uyarmıştı.
Allow me to elaborate through this snail device.
Zamanı gelince haber salyangozuyla açıklayacak olsam da...
All the waters surrounding Wano are plagued by terrible weather with no end.
Wano'yu sarmalayan deniz sahasında dinmek bilmeyen bir fırtına vardır.
The sea is rough and the current is strong...
Taşkın deniz ve şiddetli akıntılar yüzünden...
making entry into the country an ordeal!
ülkeye girmek oldukça güçtür!
What?!
Ne?!
The weather is always this bad?!
Hava hep böyle kötü mü?!
Then we should just go?!
Öylece fırtınaya mı dalacağız yani?
That's what I'm saying. Let's go!
Öyle yapalım derim! Dalalım!
Not only does it have strong samurai but it's also perilous to enter...
Hem güçlü samurayları var hem de girişi zor...
It truly is an isolated country!
İzole bir ülke olmasına şaşmamalı!
Let me think a little...
Biraz düşüneyim...
There must be a way to get through safely...
Güvenli bir şekilde geçmenin bir yolu olmalı.
What is that thing?!
Bu şey de ne böyle?!
It's an octopus!
Ahtapot!
A giant one!
Çok büyük!
Why's an octopus here?!
Ahtapotun burada ne işi var?!
We're at sea! Octopuses live here!
Denizdeyiz! Burada yaşıyorlar!
I know that, but...!
Onu biliyorum be...!
When did it come on board?!
Ne ara güverteye çıktı?
Hey! We're getting closer to Wano!
Hey! Wano'ya yaklaşıyoruz!
What?!
Ne?!
Who cares?!
Kimin umurunda?!
Go, Sunny!
İlerle, Sunny!
To Wano!
Wano'ya doğru!
Hey! Something's coming our way!
Hey! Gemiye yaklaşan şeyler var!
What?! What is it?!
Ne? Onlar da ne?
It looks like a giant fish!
Dev balıklara benziyorlar!
Is it a shark?!
Köpek balığı mı acaba?
A shark?!
Köpek balığı mı?
Oh no! It's coming!
Sıçtık! Saldırıyor!
K-K-Koi...
S-S-Sazan...
Oh my, oh my!
Muhteşem! Muhteşem!
It's a massive koi!
Kocaman sazan!
It's a school of koi?!
Sazan balığı sürüsü mü?
Why are there koi in the sea?!
Denizde sazan ne arar ki?
They're freshwater fish!
Tatlı su balığıdır!
How can they survive here?!
Buralarda nasıl yaşıyorlar?
Like it matters when we're dealing with monster koi!
Böyle canavarımsı büyüklükteki balıklara mantık söker mi?
Hey, Sanji! Are they tasty?
Hey Sanji, tatları güzel midir?
Forget about those monsters!
Canavar balıkları yemeyi aklından çıkar!
Well, alternating between baths of hot and cold water firms them up,
Onları sıcak ve soğuk suda bir süre dinlendirerek sıkılaştırıyoruz;
resulting in a delicacy called arai.
böylece "arai" diye bir lezzet elde ediliyor.
Simmering in miso makes koikoku.
Miso'yla Koikoku da yapabilirsin.
Prepared as tempura or boiled in salty-sweet sauce is also good.
Tempura ve tatlı soya sosu haşlamasıyla da iyi gider bak.
Alright!
Tamamdır!
It'll be a banquet once we see Zoro and the others again!
Zorolar'la buluştuğumuzda bu balıkla ziyafet çekeceğiz!
Don't, Luffy!
Yapma, Luffy!
Koi have a lot of tiny bones!
Sazanın kılçığı çok olur!
Who cares?!
Kimin umurunda?!
How is that even important right now?!
Bunun şu anda ne önemi var?!
Don't fight back!
Direnmesene!
Of course it fights back!
Tabii direnecek be!
Why don't you ever learn?!
Bir kere laf dinlesen ölür müsün?!
Sanji! You got Luffy all riled up, so you need to bring him back!
Sanji-kun! Senin de kabahatin var. Luffy'yi geri getir!
Don't worry, Nami.
Endişelenme, Nami-san.
He'll be fine.
Başının çaresine bakar.
What?!
Ne?!
We need to protect the ship instead!
Daha ziyade gemiyi koruyalım!
The wind is strong! Carrot, furl the sail!
Rüzgâr şiddetli! Carrot, yelkenleri topla!
Okay!
Tamamdır!
I'll help!
Yardım edeyim!
Look how clear the water is! It's like the water of a mountain river!
Şu suyun berraklığına bakın! Dağ nehrindeki suyu aratmıyor!
I'd prefer it if the water was not-so-clear! The giant fish are scaring me!
Keşke berrak olmasaydı! Dev balıklar beni korkutuyor!
What?! Wait, does that mean this is a river?
Ne? Nehre mi girdik yani?
Where are these koi heading?!
Sazanlar nereye yüzüyor ki?!
Hang on tight!
Sıkı tutunun!
We're going with the flow!
Akıntıya kapılıyoruz!
Is Luffy still around here?!
Luffy hâlâ yakınımızda mı?
What?!
Ne?
Whoa-whoa...!
Oha-çüş...!
What is that?!
Bu da ne böyle?!
The river's flowing to the bottom of the waterfall! How's that possible?!
Akan nehir, şelaleye mi bağlanıyor! Bu nasıl mümkün olabilir?!
I got it!
Anladım!
If these falls are the reason it's fresh water, then a massive source is up there!
Tatlı suyun nedeni karşımızdaki şelale ise üzerinde devasa bir havza da olmalı!
Meaning, the country of Wano is up there?!
Wano Ülkesi şelalenin ardında mı yoksa?
Up there...
Şelalenin ardı...
What?! Whaaat?!
Ne?! Nee?!
How is that possible?!
Nasıl olabilir?!
Oh! Look at that!
Ya! Şuna bakın!
The koi are climbing up the waterfall!
Sazanlar şelaleyi tırmanıyorlar!
Why?!
Nasıl be?!
Holy carp! Those koi are cool!
Muhteşem ya! Muhteşem!
A sailing ship can't do that! We'll sink under the waterfall!
Gemimiz bunu yapamaz ki! Şelalenin dibini boylarız!
You've got that right!
Herhâlde!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Wow, those are some tough koi!
Vay be, sazanlar amma güçlüymüş!
This is no time for that!
Hiç sırası değil şimdi!
Luffy! She says this ship's gonna sink!
Luffy! Gemimiz batacakmış!
Okay, I've got this!
Tamamdır, bana bırakın.
What?!
Ne?!
Hang on tight!
Sıkı tutunun bakayım!
I'm counting on you, koi!
Size güveniyorum, sazanlar!
You've got to be kidding!
Dalga geçiyorsun herhâlde!
Go!
Gidelim!
Alright!
Yaşasın!
Up we go!
Tırmanıyoruz!
What's wrong with the sea around Wano?!
Wano'nun ne biçim bir deniz sahası varmış ya?
It's so chaotic!
Çok kaotik.
Hey! There's the shore!
Hey! İşte kıyı!
– It's a whirlpool!
– Bir girdap!
Luffy! Let go of those koi!
Luffy! Sazanları sal!
No! They're my dinner!
Olmaz! Onları yiyeceğim!
Enough already!
Kes artık!
Brook! Take the helm!
Brook! Dümene geç!
Okay!
Anlaşıldı!
It's no good! The current is too strong!
Çok kötü! Akıntı çok güçlü!
Damn! We're almost there!
Lanet olsun! Varmak üzereydik!
We're not gonna make it this time...
Bu sefer kesin gidiciyiz!
Doctorine!
Doktorin!
Hey? Where are my koi?
Hey? Sazanlarım nereye gitti?
That's not important now!
Daha büyük dertlerimiz var!
Huh?
Ha?
Oh no! The whirlpool's got us!
Olamaz! Girdaba yakalanmışız!